

Contact



+95-9782662884



saisainghminetun@gm ail.com



www.facebook.com/sai.sain a.hmine.tun



in www.linkedin.com/in/s

ai-saing-hmine-tun-08b671

14b

Github github.com/SaingHmineTu

<u>n</u>

Skills

Android

Html

Javascript

Sal

Java

Css

Php

NoSQL

Languages

English

Burmese

Shan

Page 1 of 2

Sai Saing Hmine Tun

Software Developer

Lagrandia Male | 🚣 25th June, 1996 | ♀ Myanmar [Burma]

Citizenship: Myanmar [Burma]

I have experiences in developing Android Applications as well as Computer Software using Java. I also have some experiences about Front-end Web Design with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and AJAX. Currently, I'm learning PHP for Web Development and Python for Data Science and Artificial Intelligence.

Professional Experience



Java & Android Developer

TMK Group

Dec 2019 - Present

I develop Android & Computer software using Java.



ASP.Net Developer

SpectrumSoft Technologies

Jan 2018 - Nov 2018

I help a team maintain an existing ASP.Net MVC project.



Java Software Developer

72 Coder Software Co.,Ltd

May 2017 - Nov 2017

I helped a team develop POS and Eng - Myan Dictionary software for Computers using Java.

Educational History





Diploma in Cloud Computing

MIBA University

Jan 2023 - Present





Diploma in Software Engineering

Y-Max University

Oct 2022 - Present



Diploma in Information and Communication Technology

ATBC International Colleague

Oct 2022 - Present



Bachelor of Commerce

University of Economics

Jan 2013 - Jan 2017

Certifications





Introduction to Computer Science

HarvardX

Oct 2022



Postman Crash Course

Udemy

Sep 2022



Java Web Service Bootcamp

Udemy

Sep 2022



Build a Calculator using HTML, CSS and Javascript

Jdemy

Sep 2022



Professional Java Development

Brighter Myanmar

Jan 2017



Information Technology

KMD Institute

Nov 2015